Growth Strategy Copilot is an AI-assisted
growth diagnosis workspace.
It supports subscription teams from data
to strategy, experiments, and reporting.
Growth analysis often follows a repeated workflow:
define the problem, check metrics, and find bottlenecks.
Then teams segment users, prioritize strategies,
design tests, and communicate the result.
This demo uses synthetic data and mock AI.
The goal is to demonstrate the workflow.
It is not claiming real business inference
from the sample dataset.
The Diagnosis page starts with
deterministic metric calculation.
It calculates activation, paid conversion,
completion, active user rate, churn, and ARPU.
Visible rules and thresholds translate metrics
into evidence-backed decision signals.
Next, users are segmented by behavior,
payment status, recency, and price sensitivity.
Segments such as high-potential users and
churn-risk users make the diagnosis actionable.
Strategies are scored using bottleneck severity,
segment size, goal alignment, and evidence strength.
The result is a transparent P0, P1,
and P2 priority ranking.
P0 and P1 strategies become
structured A/B test plans.
Each plan includes target users, groups,
metrics, guardrails, and a decision rule.
The Report page packages the analysis into
an executive summary and detailed report.
It also provides a presentation outline
and English / Chinese localization.
Growth Strategy Copilot keeps AI support
structured, traceable, and reviewable.